Henrik Kiepe

My priority is to choose the optimal technology, and then effective implementation and testing. My main features include a very good organization of work, the ability to look for solutions and work under time pressure. Moreover, I am a flexible, independent and creative person who effectively collaborates in a team through the knowledge sharing. Currently, I would like to use and expand my skills and experience in the field of programming

hkiepe@inkontor.com

+ 48 500 552 650



www.linkedin.com/in/henrik-kiepe-20925642/



Gdańsk



PROJECTS

- Prepared a new API for borrowing in Python, with FastApi Framework https://github.com/hkiepe/fastAPI-rentalguard
- Prepared React frontend in the bike rental application https://github.com/hkiepe/rg-client
- Programmed the login function in the bike rental application in PHP https://github.com/hkiepe/rentalguard

EXPERIENCE

Inkontor Polska Sp. z o. o.

06.2015 - present

Responsibilities:

- Building the structure of the online store Magento v2.4
- Integrating systems for automatic data comparison
- Building websites using WordPress
- Online store SEO optimization
- Server administration for self-service systems on Linux Root and VHS servers
- Implementing an integrated system for accounting and warehouse management
- Monitoring external online marketing services
- Coordinating and controlling purchasing and sales processes

Manager / Owner

Bike and go-kart rental, Gdańsk / Tricity 08.2009 – present

An apprentice in finance and logistics

Fujitsu Siemens Computers GmbH 09.2008 – 04.2009

MERIT SKILLS



TRAININGS & CERTIFICATES

Python from scratch (72h). Programming school. Foundation Code: me, 02.2021 - 05.2021

JavaScript + React basic (72h). Programming school. Foundation Code: me, 11.2019 - 03.2020

Java from scratch (72h). Programming school. Foundation Code: me, 05.2019 - 06.2019

HTML5 and CSS (27h weekend). Programming school. Foundation Code: me, 03.2019 – 04.2019

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Creative and analytical thinking

Solving problems

Information synthesis and structuring

Teamwork

LANGUAGES

German – native

Polish – C2

English - C2

EDUCATION

Paderborn University, 09.2004 – 10.2010. **Diploma exam. Business Engineer.** Studies in engineering (electrical engineering) and economics.